<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<jobs>

    <job>
        <jobTitle>Order Entry Clerk</jobTitle>
        <jobBoardName>BCJobs.com website</jobBoardName>
        <jobUrl>http://www.bcjobs.com/view.php?job_id=7783</jobUrl>

        <jobDescription>Closing Date for applications: 6pm - Sunday-April-3rd&#xd;
Competitive Salary, Bonuses and Benefits&#xd;
Location: Broadway, Vancouver&#xd;
Application: Please send a cover letter and resume to careers@eminenceorganics.com&#xd;
&#xd;
&#xd;
Company Summary&#xd;
&#xfffd;minence Organic Skin Care provides premium products and unparalleled service to leading salons, spas and beauty professionals. Our products embody half a century of herbal craftsmanship and experience, and several centuries of unsurpassed skin rejuvenation techniques unique to Hungary. All of our products are handmade, using only the freshest ingredients known to nature without harming animals or using any harsh chemicals. Our ingredients are hand picked and hand harvested to ensure premium quality. Every ounce of &#xfffd;minence products receives personal attention to produce and package. We are committed to being the industry leader in keeping our planet green; from the harvest and production of our products through to packaging and delivery.&#xd;
&#xd;

Role Summary&#xd;
The Order Entry (OE) Clerk is responsible for the timely entry of all customer orders. The OE clerk receives all orders from the Inside Sales Representatives and inputs the orders ready for processing and shipping by the Warehouse. The OE clerk also processes replacement orders, gratis orders and tradeshow orders. The role has limited interaction with customers. The role generates all customer invoices and also processes payments as needed.&#xd;
&#xd;
Reporting&#xd;
This position reports directly to the Operations Lead and ultimately the Operations Manager and works in a team with several other Order Entry Clerks. &#xd;
&#xd;
Roles and Responsibilities&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Enter all orders submitted by Inside Sales Representatives (both Canadian and US)&#xd;
-	Compare data with source documents, or utilize software where possible to detect errors&#xd;

-	Locate and correct data entry errors, or report them to supervisor and/or person who submitted order&#xd;
-	Contact originators of source documents (orders) to resolve questions, inconsistencies, or missing data&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Confirm shipping charges via website quotes&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Process all Inside Sales Representative orders &#xd;
&#xfffd;	Process all other orders&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Relay invoice to Warehouse &amp; record onto electronic fulfillment form&#xd;

&#xfffd;	Backorder product in reflection of inventory levels and as per procedure&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Create invoice copies as needed and file - sales reps, original documents, backorder invoice&#xd;
&#xfffd;	File processed orders according to filing guidelines and store completed documents in appropriate locations&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Maintain logs of activities and completed work&#xd;
-	Enter all order information into customer database&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Communicate with customers regarding the details of order totals, payments and credit cards&#xd;

&#xfffd;	Facilitate Inside Sales Representatives and Outside Sales Representatives in finding information/orders/invoices and answers to order-related and accounting questions&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Receives orders from customers when Inside Sales Representatives are not available&#xd;
Accounts Receivable&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Charge credit cards as needed per order&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Apply charges to order&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Enter information into Customer Database&#xd;

&#xfffd;	Communicate with client on declined payments - daily for three days and then transfer back to Sales team&#xd;
&#xd;
&#xd;
&#xd;
Shipping &amp; Invoicing&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Assist the Operations Assistant in invoicing orders as needed &#xd;
&#xfffd;	Process and Invoice all orders occurring in any given month by month end&#xd;
Administrative Projects&#xd;

&#xfffd;	Provide data entry and administrative support and resources to assist the Customer Care, Sales, Inventory, Marketing databases and Operations projects when required&#xd;
All&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Attend departmental meetings and all other meetings&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Cross-train on all other areas in the department&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Assist with responsibilities of team members when not available&#xd;
&#xfffd;	File/pull invoices as needed&#xd;

&#xfffd;	Facilitate warehouse requests&#xd;
&#xd;
Performance Expectations&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Exemplify the &#xfffd;minence core values&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Arrive on time for shifts and meetings, take lunch as scheduled, being respectful of all &#xfffd;minence employees (operational hours are from 8.00-4.30)&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Recycle at every opportunity&#xd;

&#xfffd;	Keep commitments and meet deadlines&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Return phone calls on same day if messages left before 2pm&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Respond to all calls not returned on same day by 10am the next day&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Respond to all other customer contact (faxes, emails) within 24 hours&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Utilize Appropriate Business Language in system notes&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Process a minimum of 35 orders per day&#xd;

&#xfffd;	Process all customer orders within same day if received before 2pm&#xd;
&#xfffd;	Number of unprocessed orders will remain under 30 by the end of each day&#xd;
&#xfffd;	File all paperwork by 9am the next morning (give to Operations Assistant if no file exists)&#xd;
</jobDescription>
        <jobCity>Vancouver - Broadway</jobCity>
        <jobProvince>British Columbia</jobProvince>
        <jobEmployer>Eminence Organic Skin Care</jobEmployer>

        <jobDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 00:00:00 PST</jobDate>
        <jobCategory>Administrative/Support</jobCategory>
        <jobSalary></jobSalary>
    </job>

</jobs>